v1.69.20091202
-----------------------------------
1. [NEW] Preliminary support for SeaMonkey 2. Thank Raoul's help.
2. [NEW] Support IE7 and IE8's "Open Link a New Tab" in the context menu
3. [IMPROVEMENT] Ext. App. will show its display in context menu
4. Added French locale, thanks Alexi Haeringer.
5. Added Russian locale, thanks Raoul.

v1.63.20091024
-----------------------------------
1. [IMPROVEMENT] Significantly improved stability, many potential crash problems have been solved.
2. [BUG FIX] Open same pages in the same time in IE engine may show blank page.

v1.62.20091021
-----------------------------------
1. [IMPROVEMENT] Tools -> Options -> Content -> Enable Javascript [Advanced] -> Allow scripts to "Move or resize existing windows" will also affect IE engine. Suggested by JeePee.
2. [BUG FIX] The context menu of bookmark toolbar is not working after switched to IE engine. Reported by JeePee.
3. [BUG FIX] Firefox may crash when exiting. This is a bug of Windows XP with IE6(SP2), and I have figured out an workaround.

v1.61.20091007
-----------------------------------
1. [NEW] Support saving username and password in IE authentication dialog. Suggested by xbipin.
2. [IMPROVEMENT] Manually switched page will no longer be switched back by rules. This will also fix the bug reported by sebweber.
3. [BUG FIX] Intranet sites will not automatically switched to IE engine. To re-enable this feature, enable rule: /^http:\/\/[A-Za-z0-9]+\//
4. [BUG FIX] Type a partial url into the address bar (ie cnn instead on cnn.com) will not go to http://cnn/. See bug #21550.

v1.60.20090901
-----------------------------------
1. [NEW] Support Firefox 3.6a1.
2. [BUG FIX] Ctrl-P will invoke printer dialog twice.
3. [BUG FIX] Bug #21283 occurs again. See bug #21519.
4. Added Romanian localization, thanks Cãtãlin ZAMFIRESCU.

v1.50.20090807
-----------------------------------
1. [NEW] Support Adblock Plus in IE Tab!
2. [IMPROVEMENT] UI refined.
3. [BUG FIX] Firefox URL bar will be blank for a little while when switching to IE.
4. [BUG FIX] When doing a return carriage in case notes, it inserts a double return - ie goes down 2 lines instead of one. Thanks AuSpLaYa for reporting.
5. [BUG FIX] Can not load local html/mht file. See bug: https://www.mozdev.org/bugs/show_bug.cgi?id=21283.

v1.11.20090717
-----------------------------------
1. [BUG FIX] Ctrl-L, Ctrl-O and other some shortcuts do not work.
2. [BUG FIX] Characters require AltGr on European keyboard layouts cannot be entered.
The above bugs are reported by Meyer Kuno (Helbling Technik).
3. Support Firefox 3.5.1.

v1.10.20090714
-----------------------------------
1. [NEW FEATURE] Added a context menu for toolbar and status bar button of Coral IETab.
2. [BUG FIX] User-allowed popup window is incorrectly blocked. Thank PangooZhang for reporting.
3. [BUG FIX] Fixed Korean locale problem.

v1.01.20090707
-----------------------------------
1. [IMPROVEMENT] Now support window.opener and referer in new window. This may also fix the bug reported by HJJ0529: Can not download file from btchina.net.
2. [BUG FIX] Ctrl-Click launching External IE would fail in the 2nd time. Thanks to JackieKu for reporting.
3. [BUG FIX] Urls containing '@' are incorrectly redirected to the IE browser engine. Thanks to Meyer Kuno (Helbling Technik) for reporting.
4. [BUG FIX] Can not import settings from old IE Tab.
5. [BUG FIX] Scroll bar is incorrectly displayed in frames.
6. Added Korean locale, thank Wanoo-Lim(林完佑).
7. NOT working in the lastest nightly build of Firefox 3.6a1, so mark it only supports 3.0-3.5. I will try to support 3.6 later.

v1.00.20090531
-----------------------------------
1. No longer blocks ActiveX installation
2. Added support for script resizing, such as window.resizeTo, window.moveTo, etc. (Requires Windows XP SP2 or later)

v0.99.20090524
-----------------------------------
1. Marked Firefox 3.6 support, thanks MattPerkins for suggesting
2. Support HTTP auth, this new feature may fix the bug reported by Leo, Sch@dows and maybe also Omi Azad
3. Added zh-TW locale, thank jackbin